popdirt.com 2002-12-08

# Popdirt.com :

**·**    **What Is Your Privacy Policy?**

Popdirt.com, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. The following is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Popdirt.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address (unless you divulge this information when signing up for the Popdirt.com message boards. However, Popdirt.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). 

Popdirt.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site. Popdirt.com does not use cookies except for member login data and opinion poll cheating prevention, but the advertisers on the site may use cookies. These cookies the advertisers use do not identify you in any way, but are placed to help the advertisers find which products and services interest you. The information collected by advertisers on the site is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. 

However, as described in at the sites linked below, non-personally identifiable information collected by those advertising networks in the course of ad delivery can be associated with a user's personally identifiable information if that user has agreed to receive personally-tailored ads. 

To find out more about how our advertisers manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to: 

http://www.fastclick.com/help/privacy.html   
http://www.befree.com/docs/includes/stopspam.htm   
http://www.linkshare.com/privacy.html   
http://www.musicvision.com/network_privacy_policy.html   
http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp   
http://www.valuead.com/privacy.html   
http://valueclick.com/privacy.html   
http://www.fineclicks.com/privacypolicy1.html   
http://www.cj.com/privacy.asp   
http://smni.com/ui/privacy.asp

[ Back to Top ]
